Hallelujah!
[Amen.]
Emmanuel!
(God With Us - Matthew 1:23)
Thank you.
Hallelujah.
I want to believe that you have realised that God is reliable.
[Yes]
If God is reliable, you put your trust in Him.
How do we put our trust in God?
By using our faith to put a demand.
You can’t just say, “I trust God because I've seen so much. I have seen He is not a man”.
You can’t come to the issue of trust without using your faith to put a demand on the anointing.
Anointing is the power of God.
When you see God, you see power.
When God smiles, power smiles.
When God looks, power looks.
When God moves, power moves.
That is God!
Glory be to God.
God is honest, reliable, trustworthy and stable.
Therefore, what is lacking is not greater faith but a greater God.
Are you with me?
Tell your neighbour,
“What is lacking is not greater faith but a greater God, big God – G O D.”
The SCOAN Sunday Service
If you have realised that God is honest, based on you have seen - what else again?
God is honest, stable, trustworthy and reliable.
Therefore, what is lacking is not greater faith,
because you demand greater faith - no,
but a greater God.
Viewers all over the world, I know you are at home.
When I say "at home" I mean in Him.
Your home is not here.
This reminds me of the woman with the issue of blood.
She believed enough.
You say, "I believe".
What do you mean by "believe"?
You believe enough.
She believed enough and pressed through the crowd to touch Jesus.
There was so much crowd. "How would I go? I don't want to push. I'm not strong".
But she believed enough to press through crowd to touch who?
To touch who?
To touch Jesus.
Press in to touch Jesus.
Tell your neighbour, "Press in to touch Jesus."
I cannot hear you.
[Press in to touch Jesus.]
Tell your neighbour.
Press in to touch Jesus to heal and deliver you.
I cannot hear you.
[Press in to touch Jesus to heal and deliver you.]
Say, “I press in to touch Him. Oh, Lord Jesus, heal me!”
The SCOAN Sunday Service
Yes, what is good her is good for you.
The Bible says that she believed enough – not just believed – she believed enough to press in.
There was so much crowd, not only crowd - hindrance, obstacle...
If it was a gentle crowd... but this one the Bible called a throng.
There was so much noise; you could see a thug, you could see a street boy.
A lot of them were following Jesus...
The Bible says that she believed enough to press through; through what?
Crowd.
To touch Jesus.
You must press in to touch Him to heal you.
Say, “I believe”.
[I believe.]
I cannot hear you.
You must believe enough.
I press in to touch You, oh Lord; heal me.
Say after me, "I press in to touch You."
Write it down - that should be your prayer point today.
I press in to touch You, oh Lord Jesus; heal, deliver and bless me.
Let Your seraphim touch me.
I press it to touch You, oh Lord; heal me.
It is Jesus
Yes it is Jesus
In my soul
For I have touched
The hem of His garment
And His blood
Has made me whole
Your voice.
It is Jesus
Yes it is Jesus
In my soul
For I have touched
The hem of His garment
And His blood
Has made me whole
It is Jesus
Yes it is Jesus
In my soul
For I have touched
The hem of His garment
And His blood
Has made me whole
I press in to touch You; Jesus, heal me.
I press in to touch You; Jesus, deliver me.
I press in to touch You; Jesus, bless me.
Let Your seraphim touch me, in Jesus’ name.
Be ready for a touch.
Are you ready?
[Yes.]
You may be seated.
Thank you.
What is your name?
My name is Favour Okere.
Good. What happened?
I have the problem of scoliosis of my spine.
My spine is curved; and I am sure that God will help me.
Remove the world "sure".
OK?
Say, "I believe."
I believe.
I believe that God will heal me.
You say after me, "I press in to touch Him, oh Lord, heal me."
Stretch your hand.
I press in to touch Him, oh Lord, heal me.
Rise up.
Remove it.
Let her remove it by herself.
Touch your body again.
I press in to touch You...
That "You" is Jesus, OK?
"I press in to touch You, oh Lord, heal me."
Amen.
You can go.
Healed In Jesus’ Name
Yes, this is exactly what the woman with the issue of blood said.
Jesus said, “Somebody touched Me, ...
Let someone say it.
[Somebody touched me!]
I cannot hear you.
... for I perceive power has gone out from Me”.
Let somebody say, "Somebody touched Me".
I cannot hear you!
[Somebody touched me!]
Thank you.
Yes. When the woman said, "I press in touch you, oh Lord, heal me",
immediately Jesus said, "Somebody touched me".
Please man of God help me.
I have a stiff neck due to spondylolysis
I have been booked for an operation.
I also have spinal cord stenosis.
The doctor said that if I am not operated on time it would affect my spinal cord and I become parallelized.
Help me man of God.
Please man of God help my husband.
He has been booked for an operation.
He has stiff neck and stenosis of the spinal cord.
OK. Come on.
Stand up.
Listen to your little one.
OK. Say, "I press in to touch You, oh Lord, heal me."
I press in to touch You, oh Lord, heal me.
Healed In Jesus’ Name
Somebody touched Me, for I perceive power has gone out from Me.
Thank You, Jesus.
I am healed.
I can now turn my head.
I can now bend forward and backward.
What are we learning?
Faith – your faith is growing.
You are now seeing that Jesus is reliable.
Man of God, I have a dislocation of the elbow joint due to accident...
Where were you going?
I was at work.
Come on.
Stand up.
You listened to the message?
Yes, Sir.
What the messages is all about?
It is about pressing on to hold on to my faith.
You are pressing in this time, not on.
You have to press in, because the situation is tough, because your faith is not strong.
You cannot press on.
I press in.
I press in to hold on to faith.
Healing In Jesus’ Name
OK, remove it - you are free.
Come on, you can go.
Thank You, Jesus.
Man of God, I have spondylolysis.
Healing In Jesus’ Name
Stand up!
Come on!
Look here!
You can go.
Turn your neck, you are free.
Healed In Jesus’ Name
Thank You, Jesus.
I am suffering from lumbar scoliosis.
You say what?
I am suffering from lumbar spondylolysis.
I thought that I am the only person that doesn't know how to spell it - that...
I have a colleague now.
This spondylolysis - I have looked at it in my dictionary "to get it easy".
It is very difficult for me.
But now I find someone who is my partner :)
How do you call it?
Spondulosis.
Lumbar ?spondulosis?
?Cororosis?
:)
The SCOAN Sunday Service
Stand up.
You are my partner.
OK, it's all right.
Thank You, Jesus.
OK, It's all right.
Come on.
Thank you.
Healing In Jesus’ Name
OK, it's all right. Stand up.
Healed In Jesus’ Name
Man of God, help my mother.
She is having difficulties in walking.
OK, it's all right. Come on!
Healing In Jesus’ Name
Look here!
It's all right.
Stand.
Remove this from...
The SCOAN Sunday Service
Thank You, Jesus!
Thank You, Jesus for healing my mother.
Thank You, Jesus Christ.
Thank You, Jesus.
Let someone say, “I press in to touch You, oh Lord; free me.”
Somebody touched Me, for I perceive power has gone out from Me.
Yes, He senses power.
Somebody touched Me
Somebody touched my soul
When I was praying
Praying to my Father
Somebody touched my soul
It must be Jesus
Jesus Christ touched my soul
When I was praying
Praying to my Father
Jesus Christ touched my soul
Somebody touched Me,
I cannot hear you.
Somebody touched Me
Somebody touched Me, for I perceive power has gone out from Me.
Somebody touched Me!
Who?
Me.
Glory be to God.
[Amen.]
It is time now to continue your mediation in your heart.
What are you meditating?
Lord Jesus, make me Your channel – a channel of pardon.
Make me Your channel – a channel of forgiveness.
Make me You channel – a channel of purity, oh, Lord Jesus.
Simple - those are the things you should meditate on.
You may be seated while your meditation goes on.
That is the only way you can be delivered.
The kind of prayer you offer nowadays cannot help you.
You are used to...
All those things cannot help you.
If this thing could help you, it would have helped you.
Tell your neighbour, "If this prayer could help you, it would have helped you".
You know, you have been in it...
This can not help you.
You need meditation to get out of this mess.
Tell your neighbour, "You need meditation to get out of this mess."
If Jesus is Spirit you need to begin to make that noise.
But you shout "Jesus" not in church but at home, as He were your neighbour.
Those things are hypocritical.
People choose to be religious, from where we all came from.
We were religious men, before we turned to Christianity.
Today, people are going back to their religious systems.
There is hypocrisy in it.
There is no unity, envy jealousy among the churches,
"This one is devil.
This one is satan."
Who is now a child of God?
The devil and satan now turned to be a child of God.
There is so much hypocrisy, disunity...
Meditation is a visit with God.
Tell your neighbour.
[Meditation is a visit with God.]
This is why the Bible says, “Pray without ceasing”.
Prayer is a thing of the heart, not a thing of the body.
Today's prayer becomes the thing of the body, but it is a thing of a heart.
I can be talking to you now, but I am praying at the same time.
How this is possible?
I'm talking to you and at the same time I'm praying.
It is possible because a prayer is the thing of the heart.
Our heart can do 10 things at the same time – it is a place of God, it is a place of meditation,
it is a place of communion.
it is a place of holiness,
it is a place of direction,
it is a place of ministry – that is heart.
If you say you must shout when you pray, how do you pray when you sleep?
And you are also supposed to pray while you are sleeping.
The way blood runs in our system is the way prayer should also run.
It is an integral part.
It is an article of faith.
These are the things you need to break through.
You need to get this right to be saved.
If not, satan knows when you are not praying and he will catch you.
He will never catch you while you are praying;
he knows you do not pray all the time, you have a time for prayer.
Those times you are not praying, he normally catches you.
When you look at the problems you had, they were at times you were not praying.
You say, "I am going to pray."
Before you get there satan catches you.
Satan knows those things and he had been catching you like that.
This is why 90% of attacks today are in the dream.
Because he know that you are empty while you are sleeping.
When they attack you in the dream, the thing will manifest in the real life.
When one was attacked yesterday night, the thing will start manifesting today.
If it was a gun shoot, it will start manifesting and it will happen in one of the following days.
It might have been a food given to you in the dream; when you wake up the thing will begin to manifest.
Something like that ... definitely.
They decided to attack you in the dream because they know you do not have the power of meditation.
When you meditate, you meditate throughout and when you sleep, meditation continues
because it is a power of God; it is not your power.
This prayer you offer today is your own power, not God's power.
Therefore, you can not operate in the dream.
When you meditate and finally sleep, the meditation will continue
because it is your heart that is doing it.
Your heart will never cease while sleeping.
Your heart functions while you are sleeping and the same heart is the one of mediation.
Your body ceases immediately when you sleep but the heart continues.
Meditation is of heart.
That meditation will become revelation that manifests through your life.
Where there is darkness, and you ask God to make you a channel of light - there is an attack from darkness
- you just see a manifestation of it because you are a channel of light to God.
Heart needs to be delivered to meditate.
Tell your neighbour.
[Heart needs to be delivered to meditate.]
To meditate.
Heart that is H E A R T.
Heart means your spirit.
Tell your neighbour.
[Heart means your spirit.]
When I say heart I mean your spirit.
Man's spirit means heart.
Your heart needs to be delivered to meditate because a lot of things are going on in your heart.
To receive is very simple – healing and deliverance are on your table already;
how will you maintain them?
You can not maintain even your life, your hair, your dress, your suit - you can not maintain.
You cannot even maintain your home.
You cannot maintain children given to you by God.
You cannot maintain your husband or your wife.
You cannot maintain the car you have.
Not to mention heavenly resources.
You cannot maintain your business, salary, the money you receive.
Even your shoes - you cannot maintain them.
It is better not to receive than to receive without what?
[Maintenance.]
It is better not to...
If I want to give you this.
If you know you cannot maintain it - don't receive it.
You can only receive it when you know you can maintain it
because you will need it more dearly tomorrow, not today.
What you are about receive today, you will need so dearly tomorrow.
Today you need healing - it is true, you need healing.
But you need a better one tomorrow.
If you now lose it at the time you need it most - what is the use of it?
That is why we are talking of maintenance.
Yes.
Meditation is a tool you can use to receive from God.
Meditation is a tool you can use to receive from Heavenly Father.
What are we meditating on?
The word of God.
If anyone tells you that you can meditate without heart, that is not meditation; it is thinking.
Thinking is in lower-house, meditation is upper-house – heart.
Thinking is a sitting room, meditation is a bed room.
The SCOAN Sunday Service
If I were just a visitor, you would not allow me to enter your bed room.
You will receive me in your sitting room, entertain me and do whatever you want to do and discharge me.
But I must be a part of the house before I can enter your bed room.
Meditation is a bed room, thinking is a sitting room.
This is why we say the Word must be an integral part of you – live in you, dominate you, rule you.
When you are delivered, your heart will be free.
[Amen.]
Meditation can only work when you have a free spirit – free heart.
A free heart meditates.
Tell your neighbour.
[A free heart meditates.]
A free spirit meditates.
[A free spirit meditates.]
You think, "How will I solve my problem? I own a debt. I'm tired of this world.
All my family - we are poor."
All this thinking...
You need to leave all this for God.
When you leave it for God, He is able; you can meditate with your heart.
This is what I mean by self-will.
Self-will around your heart will never allow your heart to meditate.
We meditate in the power of God when our heart is free.
And one’s heart can be free when we are delivered.
STANDARD FOR LIFE